whetstoneeducation.com 2015-04-07

# Whetstone Education

**WHETSTONEEDUCATION.COM Privacy Policy**

Whetstone Education, LLC (“ ** _Whetstone_** ” or “ ** _we_** ”, “ ** _our_** ” or “ ** _us_** ”) is committed to ensuring the privacy of those customers who use the Whetstone website (“ ** _Users_** ”) located at http://www.whetstoneeducation.com (the “ ** _Whetstone Site_** ”).  This Privacy Policy (“ ** _Policy_** “) describes what information is collected from Users and how that information is used and disclosed. By using the Whetstone Site, you consent to the terms of this Policy.  Although this Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights, it does serve as an expression of Whetstone’s commitment to protecting private personal information.

**NOTICES**

**_Notice to California Residents_** : Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (1) a list of the categories of information, such as name, address, e-mail address, and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please write to us with a reference to California Disclosure Information at: Whetstone Education, LLC, 4035 Washington Ave, New Orleans, LA 70125.

California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (“ ** _California Act_** ”) and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by the California Act, this Privacy Policy identifies the categories of personally identifiable information that we collect through our website about individuals who use or visit our website and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom such personally identifiable information may be shared.

**Authorized Users**

Minors under eighteen (18) years of age are prohibited from using this site. The Whetstone Site is not intended for children under the age of 18.  If you are under 18 years old, please do not provide personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever on the Whetstone Site.

**Information We Collect**

  1. User Provided Information.  Users may provide to Whetstone what is generally called “personally identifiable” information if you register with or contract for services with Whetstone.

  * Individual Users.  For example, during the registration process, individual Users, including administrators, coaches/observers, and teachers, will be prompted to create an account with a password and username.  Your username will be disclosed to others.  You are required to keep your password secret.  In addition, Whetstone may give Users the option to provide us with certain demographic information about yourself or your organization.  We may enable you to supply information about yourself on a personal profile page.  Information that you may be able to disclose might include the following: your personal interests, gender, age, educational institution, pictures, videos, tastes, preferences and other information.  We encourage you to submit relevant information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site, but you should be cautious in submitting personal information to areas viewable by others. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in your personal profile.
  * Student Information.  We may also collect and store information about Users’ students (“Student Information”) such as name, contact information, performance and comments/notes to the extent such Student Information is provided by Users, in which Whetstone will comply with applicable provisions of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. § 1232g; 34 CFR Part 99).
  * Other Integrations or Applications.  Whetstone may allow you to integrate certain other online profiles in certain cases. In those cases, you will be subject to the privacy policies of those third party websites and/or applications. Please consult the privacy policies of any third party websites and/or applications before using them to send information to others through the Whetstone Site.  Your personally identifiable information may be visible to others through these third party integrations and applications on the Whetstone Site.

  1. Aggregate Data.  Aggregate data is data we collect about a group or category of features, services or individuals, from which individual identities have been removed. For example, information about how you use a feature may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same feature, without any personal information included in the resulting data.  Whetstone uses aggregate data to help identify trends and understand User needs so we can provide better features and services.

Whetstone may also share automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist them in understanding how people and organizations make certain choices, educational policies, teaching methods, teacher observation rubrics, the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Whetstone Site or for purposes of other persons or entities in the education industry.  Whetstone may also collect demographic data or information, including, without limitation, income, disabilities, educational attainment, home ownership, employment status, hobbies, interests, product ownership and location.

  1. General User Data.  General User Data, such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system and browser type, and the date and time of your visit, may be automatically collected through the use of “cookies” (small files that are stored on your computer by a website to give you a unique identification). Cookies also keep track of services you have used, record registration information regarding your login name and password, ensure you do not repeatedly see advertisements, record your preferences and keep you logged into the Whetstone Site.  We treat general user data as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the personally identifying information mentioned above and, in those cases, will only use it as aggregate data.

**Disclosure of Information**

We do not sell, rent or share personally identifiable information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy. We may share personally identifiable information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business.  These functions may include: analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and processing payment transactions.  In all cases we limit the information shared with our third-party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions.  We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with this Policy, we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information, and we require these parties to use any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  We are not responsible for any information you provide to third party vendors or other users directly, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them.

We may share automatically collected, demographic and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist them in understanding how people and organizations make choices and other educational enrichment research purposes, as well as for the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Whetstone Site.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include, without limitation, fulfilling orders, sending communications on our behalf (including our e-mail communications), analyzing data, providing marketing, or service assistance, creating, and providing customer service.  These third parties may have access to our users’ personally identifiable information in order to provide these services to us or on our behalf.

Except as stated in this Policy, we do not share personally identifiable information about Users with third parties unless we reasonably believe that doing so is legally required or is in Whetstone’s interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.

In addition, information about our Users, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, equity or debt financing or sale of Whetstone assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets.

**Third Parties/External Websites**

The Whetstone Site may contain links to external websites, and areas where you can provide information to third-parties.  These are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties or third party sites.  Any personal information you provide in such areas, and on such linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy.  Please learn about the privacy and security practices and policies of external websites and third-parties before providing them with personal information.

**User Profile and Password**

If you register as a User, you can update, correct, or delete your user information and email subscription preferences by going to the log-in section of the Whetstone Site and consistent with the other policies and agreements governing your use of the Whetstone Site.

User registration information is accessible online only through the use of a password.  To protect the confidentiality of your personal information as a User, we recommend that you keep your password confidential.

**Security**

We use reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control.  However, we cannot guarantee protection of all information in all cases.  For example, we cannot guarantee protection against interception, misappropriation, misuse, or alteration, or that your information will not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.  Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.  Additionally, we have absolutely no control over the security of other sites you might visit, interact with or do business with.

If we learn of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps.  Whetstone may post a notice on the Whetstone Site if a security breach occurs.  We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances.  Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.  To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us.

**Policy Changes**

We will modify this Policy if our privacy practices materially change. We will notify you of such changes by posting the new policy on the Whetstone Site and indicating the date it was last updated at the bottom of the Policy. We encourage you to review the Policy each time you visit the Whetstone Site to see if it has been updated, in order to make sure you understand how personal information you provide will be used.

**Additional Information**

If you have any questions about this Policy, or the practices of or your dealings with the Whetstone Site, please email us at [elavin@whetstoneeducation.com] or write us at:

Whetstone Education, LLC

4035 Washington Ave

New Orleans, LA 70125
